Please, Gio, these humans saved me.
I'm aware.
Dolan, we seem to have
entered an elf forest.
Yeah, but it's okay.
We didn't come here to fight, after all.
Still, you two should get
behind me just in case.
My human and lamia friends.
Firstly, let me express my gratitude for
the help you provided our friend Merl.
Thank you.
But Ente belongs to us forest dwellers.
Why have you set foot in this place?
Visitors from the Dark
I'm Dolan, from Verun Village.
Some disturbing monsters have started
appearing in the vicinity of our village.
We surmised that something was going on
in the forest and came to investigate,
but I realize now that we should've
asked for your permission first.
I apologize for that.
I see. I cannot blame you for
coming here for such a reason.
But I will suggest that you leave, at once.
Because this forest is currently
in an extremely perilous state.
Are you talking about the demon troops?
I see. So they've appeared
in your village, too?
"Appeared" doesn't begin to describe it.
We're currently waging war against
the demon army in this forest.
Wait! How are you dealing with it?
Do you have enough forces?
Have you reported this
emergency to the kingdom?
Is your village truly safe?!
Christina!
Calm down!
Look, the elves seem troubled.
Even one of that bizarre
creature is dangerous,
and there's a whole army of them?
Tell me, is your village not in
extreme danger as we speak?!
If there is anything we can
do to help, we'll do it!
Oh, forgive me. I lost my composure.
It's not a bad thing.
You're worried for the elves, aren't you?
Merl, those humans seem nice.
They are. What's more,
they even beat the demon soldiers.
Yeah, that human girl seems to
have real skill with the sword.
Right. And it looks like
that lamia likes them.
Maybe we can trust them.
Chris's strength of character
is helping us here.
But did they say "demon army"?
If those zerts earlier didn't just
happen to wander onto the surface,
that must mean there's a portal connecting
the demonic realm to this Forest of Ente.
Should the portal open fully, even
stronger demons will come through.
No... I'll destroy them
before it comes to that!
Even if people find out that I have a
dragon soul and I'm chased out of my home,
I have to use my dragon
powers without hesitation.
I have a proposal.
As she just said, this is an emergency.
It isn't something you
can handle on your own.
This may violate your laws, but would
you allow us to help you temporarily?
But...
Brother.
Fio?
I understand your
responsibilities as our leader.
But I care more about our
fellow villagers than our laws.
I think these people are speaking in
good faith. Let's try trusting them.
I understand.
Please, my human friends.
Lend us your strength.
But, knowing that you can hold your own,
I'll surely begin to rely on you...
even though it may put your lives in peril.
And we're saying that's fine by us.
I'm Gio, brave human boy.
Dolan. Nice to meet you.
What was that?!
Dolan... What is that?
This sensation...
I recognize it.
A portal has opened!
To the village!
Hear me, O laws of wind.
Give us a tailwind to boost our travels.
Wind Accel!
A wind support magic.
It should help us hurry.
Huh... so this is the surface.
Not too shabby.
So that our demonic ruler might
obtain the Ente Yggdrasil,
we shall serve as the vanguard
that clears the way.
Remember that.
It is a clear display of his trust in us.
We need to repay it by doing
our jobs as mercenaries!
Where is Georg?
Not here yet. His stupid amount of
mana's probably slowing him down.
Well, in that case, let's play a
little game before he shows up.
I can sense the elves nearby.
How about we see who can find them first?
If I find them first, I'm free to kill them?
That's the prize!
I'm in. Gellen?
I have no interest in weaklings.
I'm only here to fulfill
my mission to the letter.
Hmph! Well, I'm gonna raise some hell!
Starting with those trees there!
Such an impatient fellow.
This place smells nice, however.
The lovely fragrance of flowers...
It makes me want to show them some love.
Damn these bugs! There's no end to them!
Don't let a single one into the village!
Wha... What is that?
I am the first of the
Four Demonic Knights, Geolude!
My attack shall signal
the declaration of war!
F-Fire!
What? Is that true, my spirit friends?
The spirits are reporting that fiends
are attacking from north of the village.
Dolan, these must be the
higher-level demons you spoke of.
We need to hurry.
Let's enter the village from the
southwest and fortify the defenses.
Dolan!
Right!
Fight them off!
You could handle the troops,
but not a single blow from me?
Your screams just now were
music to my ears, elves!
You can have the privilege of
witnessing my spear once more!
Die!
Curses!
R-Roses?
Quit spacing out and run!
How vexing!
Do you really believe mere vines
can restrain the great Geolude?!
Curses... They absorb my
blood and mana to bloom?
Such loathsome black roses!
Diadora...
We're almost to the village!
Stay on your toes!
Right!
I beseech thee, O laws of power.
Give me countless arrows to smite my foes.
Energy Rain!
Hurry up and get in!
We should buy some time.
I was thinking the same.
Me, too!
Christina, Celina, let's use these
to cast some powerful spells.
Magic crystals? And pure ones, at that.
Are these the ones we found at that swamp?
Exactly.
Use them as you will.
Heed my words, O laws of wind.
Allow me to bind and turn
you into my blades!
Go wild!
Tornado!
O spirits of earth, my foes are your own.
Sharpen thyself and be my spear!
I can't let them outdo me.
Heed my words, O laws of power.
Come to me and gather,
and erupt into flames.
Explosion!
Incredible.
Those feats of strength make me
want to rely on you even more.
We wanted to show that you could rely on us.
Dweller of the demonic realm, do you
realize the sins you have committed?
You left flora and insects
crushed in your wake,
killed animals, and took lives from
those who call the forest their home.
You have committed too many sins to count!
Sins, you say?
Perhaps you consider them sins, Diadora.
But to me, being weak is a greater sin!
They were killed because they were weak!
How you make me laugh!
Enough. Your very words
are a blight on my ears.
Allow me to inform you of
one another sin, then.
You are weak.
Oh, right. Your appearance
in this realm was one, too.
Perish, filthy demon!
You played around too much, Geo!
Wow, you really held Geo down?
You must have really powerful
mana, rose spirit.
How lovely.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm one of the
Four Demonic Knights, Raflasia.
Let's play nice, milady.
Oh...
Wow.
This is our elven village.
But we have no time for sightseeing.
Yes.
Hmph! I had no need for your help, Raflasia.
I could've handled that myself!
My, such an obvious bluff.
But it is your role to charge ahead
and get into trouble, I suppose.
No, my role is to massacre
our foes before anyone else!
You're the only one who believes that.
Now...
Are you ready for a world of hurt,
my black rose lady?
Oh, you're teaming up?
Then I shall take you on
with my friends, too!
Hear me, flora spirits of the forest.
Come to me and put on a show of strength...
What's the matter? Answer me, forest flora!
Wait, are you calling out
to these floral spirits?
I saw a bunch of pretty
flowers on the way here,
and I just had to have some
fun with them, you see!
This lily spirit here
withered away screaming.
And this gentian spirit was crying
for help as it rotted away.
And the white lily spirits were
chopped to pieces by the zerts.
Why, you...
Oh, but the red roses were the
most devoted of them all.
They cried, "Diadora! Please help, Diadora,"
as I slowly cursed them to death.
How dare you?!
All those lives you took
belonged to my friends and family!
How dare you!
So much anger, and for such a silly reason!
All flowers fight over the
nutrients in the soil to grow.
You should be glad that your
competition has dwindled.
You know what? You should be
thanking me, if anything.
Silence! You will pay for what you've done!
Not a speck of you shall remain!
You know, I'm a floral spirit, too.
But, unlike you, my flower isn't one
that grows in the paradise up here.
I'm the spirit of a demonic realm flower
that only feeds on blood and life,
the raflaora!
All life exists to feed my
blooming—they are but sacrifices.
As you now see.
What?!
Insanity is doing the same thing
and expecting different results.
I thank you for the delicious food,
just as I did the other flowers.
You're going down!
Gosh, will you ever learn?
Go!
You're the one who needs to learn.
The prettier a rose, the sharper its thorns.
People have said so forever.
You'd best commit it to memory.
Blood...
My blood?
You scarred me?
Unthinkable! Unforgivable!
How dare a lowly surface rose
spirit tarnish my beauty!
You have committed the gravest of sins!
You don't say.
Your indignation is utterly
meaningless, if you ask me.
I've decided to kill every last one of you.
This is tedious, Raflasia!
I'll end this with one swing of my spear!
Wait, Geo! She's mine!
Die!
Don't think those vines will work on
me without the element of surprise!
Come on!
You should flee more desperately...
or this won't be any fun at all!
Wh-What? My mana's been absorbed...
I'll bestow you a painless death.
Die!
I can't die before I avenge
my friends and family.
I'm so sorry, everyone.
Wh-What?!
A h-human?
Next Episode
This week's lucky item is magic crystals!
Look forward to next time!